Scopus
but I'm distracted happy distracted guys
the Aeons watching you
we got to have your minds right yeah
Oh 2021 would you people showing a bit
more bet no also without mob is about
the transparent yeah
it blinked on distracted for a second
that I think it was I don't know where I
was looking I wouldn't have considered
myself
all right look guys
even beyond our super torque levels case
finally releasing the secret good open
pile of the secret code of the press
event you're gonna see it's gonna be
it's very exciting what we're gonna
release big release really something
that sets the tone for what we'll be
doing for the next year
yes I will show you will show you we're
gonna disable driver monitoring if
you're stopped I'm like we're not
monitoring you due to some states laws
but um but if I do it's not disabled
right now so you'll see what happens
[Music]
very bad very bad
should we kick them out well you don't
want to because like I'm not saying we
kicked them out I'm saying that like I
don't think we should do that I think
once it gets to read yeah we shouldn't
like like disengage we should job is to
continue to do the brakes but we
shouldn't go back to green we shouldn't
go back to the yeah we can and we can't
go into like a final stage where you're
into a state where it'll stay red until
it detects that I step on a pedal or hit
the wheel well but that's what you know
it doesn't know it it let me get to red
and it let me get to beeping oh you're
saying once you get to that do you can
you set up but you can't restart now
once you get to revenues you're saying
once you get to red even after you look
straight you have to actually take
control of vehicle I think is that
policy oh okay so you you for seduction
disengage you force the disengagement
absolutely yeah yeah this would super
booster it's really good look like super
clears when it's pulsing green yeah it's
fine
forcing green yeah but once it gets to
red now it should be slowing down and it
shouldn't let me it shouldn't let me
like that was too easy
that was way too easy for me to get
control back move me to get back at all
yes that's our oh yeah we can do that
yeah that's like forcing you so but you
keep beeping you keep beeping are you
after yeah nobody know I'm told but if
that's the point that's the point now we
might be when maybe I'll give them a
little bit more time like maybe it's
like green yellow red right whereas it's
beeping and you can still look forward
again I don't know though I kind of
think once it gets to beeping I have to
put my hands on the wheel and disengage
no you got you gotta actually take
control the car that's it if you want to
go if you don't go you don't have to
yeah we can do that yeah that's the
policy decision and then if you get
three of those on the drive yeah
what a great feature of super cruise you
guys remember that periscope when I got
locked out of super Cruiser I was
devastated
what but the super cruise localities you
have a war stand it hasn't won because I
have to stop we have to stop for a
minute mom we could do that too yeah how
brutal should be they pay attention guys
I'm so watch my don't pay attention
yeah yeah see that was too easy done
no it's too easy for me to get no no
that didn't punish me enough I should
have to drive the car for at least 10
seconds yeah that's right pay attention
for a second
Wow no false positives they're true
negatives either driving wandering so
good it's great it's not so hard to
detect when somebody's distracted from
something I don't know like gray zones
where yeah when you drive and you pay
attention just look straight especially
if you're on the highway yeah you guys
Tesla needs us yeah is the PF net no
well actually yes is PF yes yeah
we're not when I use a PI controllers
anymore we're using PF controllers like
PID controllers but better
oh man I love driving monitoring guys oh
and by the way there should be no
six-minute a minute all right well there
you see if you set off so what we're
gonna do if driver monitoring is not
working on you for some reason I think
the policy we're gonna ship is a three
minute time out now I mean as our driver
monitoring gets better and we grow more
confident in it we're going to make that
period shorter and shorter children
till eventually he will let you engage
unless it detects that you are an active
driver participating in the driving
experience because guys all self-driving
cars today are level to pay attention
all talks today we got so what what
happen if you look down but you keep
your head straight not doing eye
tracking yet we're not trying to catch
all of them look like can you cheat the
system
yeah can you cheat GM SuperCrew system
yeah but this is mostly to prevent you
know most people are using a phone look
down here watch the merge make sure it
doesn't has it all distracted you so we
just don't want people to do that as
part of well there's great things to be
announced at the press which are
obviously not gonna route bus boy I want
announce right now this card by the way
is running the secret good version of
open pilot I was just trying yeah I
looked over the CEO piece I was
distracted very punishing well yeah I
don't think we should go to read and
just that quickly so we a wholesome
green for a bit what you look at what
super cruises policy is yeah I belong to
think is that you do not is the super
response minutes right in front of you
it is easier to notice that's true
but you know certainly once they get to
rad they got to drive the car
made bad choices
yeah there's guys what do you think is a
secret good personable
well okay so
actually your secret charge you have I I
feel the wobble what well there's a
permit and a signet parameter change but
I don't want to tell you because I don't
want to bias you if I do want to know
what you think you add is it plus twenty
centimeters nothing I actually like it
it's wobbling a little more on
straightaways it feels better in turns
yeah so I made this tonight cos point
five which is what it's always so that's
what is always speed on all this okay it
does feel better in turns and it feels
worse on trees so it should be more
Center because basically it forgives a
lot more we have like vodka parameters
if the model is incorrect or far away
but yeah I mean you know we can we can
measure this
the turns feel better the turns
definitely feel well time with secret
good open pilot yeah I got the
disengagement oh really yeah yeah we
definitely know that's really bad guys
we don't have any unplanned disengage
this one of these go to super cruise and
you can cruise forever now that you have
driver monitoring it's drive monitoring
my scope is my you show me you that's
right don't be distracted don't do it
guys the end some of these props people
dynamic than what they are today
definitely working on some parameter
features yeah it all depends on the new
location architecture which is also the
new calibration architecture oh this is
much better insurance yeah
I don't even go enough drives like every
night working on
making sure the pilot 0.5 is good
okay I was scratching my head he's fresh
event ma'am at the halfway mark guys the
halfway mark that's all it is
we're not gonna tell you what the press
event is you got to be the press
you got to be invited we've invited four
we've invited four groups for presses
hopefully they all accept our lovely
offer I'm not sure why you wouldn't but
now one of them won't so we won't get a
new press in
if you have a press and put it this way
if you know how to get us a million
views on YouTube we're trying to get
some million viewer videos I've been
here right 1 million views it's a good
number of views what happen if you fall
asleep with your head straight well so
Ryan's an asshole yeah literally no I
literally want you to fall asleep with
your head straight it's impossible your
head goes like this and you're
distracted yeah I've tried on airplanes
many times to fall asleep with my head
straight you can't do it that's living
on plane otherwise can you wear
sunglasses with the system was yes
that's lie again we specifically look at
the head orientation and terms out that
you really catch like 95 or more percent
of the situation where if I had a flea
I would definitely make sure my fleet
happiness how do you have a fleet
without you know if you're paying people
to drive please look at the road
yeah so I think we'll disable it if
we're going like lower than a certain
speed
anything's - for action of every commit
the closest be dependent yeah it's worse
to be distracting you going Saturday
we're going ten yes like you media type
of timing yeah
it's a distance kind of thing yeah
yeah well I'm so I'm definitely gonna
put something that like when you go to
zero speed you decide the time that you
keep you basically like I said whatever
it's building yeah should we do it talks
about the six minutes you think wait a
minute like every time they at least not
counting when you're stopped like the
six minutes count their Oh shouldn't
count what you're stopped or I
understand
maybe guys look at the secret good
version of a pilot it's so good and that
will be not in the geofence wheel driver
monitoring incorporates showing
placement to ensure a proper field of
view but so if you follow the mounting
is Tatiana you have the right mounting
procedure and you have the right you can
also enable front camera upload please
enable front camera upload people we
love your data we don't have enough data
this net is trained on too little data
we've taught we train this net on a
really paltry amount of people it's
amazing that it works as well as it does
so this is my plea for data please
data we love data and then you can also
you'll be able to review your front
camera so you'll know what your
placement is you'll make sure it's good
if you upload the data to us
what else is that data data data we love
data please please give me your data
people with definition if you just go
grab the camera that's a distracted
we're engaged again it doesn't detect if
you're distracted when you're not
engaged I think that's gonna be a toggle
yeah yes we're gonna have two toggles
for driver monitoring well actually yeah
we cannot allow people to disable when
is good enough yeah I think I think
we'll still write beta for it yeah we'll
just make that we'll make that time
increasingly aggressive to to encourage
people to turn it on I mean they will
have another toggle which will stay
forever and that'll be an able driver
monitoring while I'm not engaged yeah
Scheffer plus will also have that toggle
as well so Scheffer plus will have
dragon monitoring and no ways in Spotify
because those are gone
and we need all that room to run all
this fancy driver monitoring stuff
that's a line drive about our stuff is
really small
we're driving right into the Sun right
now yeah okay
yeah
yeah there is somebody who wants an
interposition the application try to
give you a job at cutting-edge overcome
I can't say
you see both driver money when you turn
signal on that's a good idea
yeah I mean you also shouldn't be using
your turn now
no is it driving well okay so there's
the driver bottoming would not engage
policy which I think can do things like
that but the driver moment why are you
using a turn signal while you're engaged
only if you want to change lanes right
now when you're changing lanes you
shouldn't look away from longer than the
driver I mean that is a nice thing about
having an ACC system I wonder how many
accidents that prevent they prevent
where people are changing lanes hooking
in their blind spot the person in front
of the brakes I mean that's one of the
main reasons because I'd like to have
HTC always on all the time yeah because
you like use your to more set of eyes
looking site when you don't look one eye
in the EON it's just an eye future
products they have more eyes
just hides right notic not years yes oh
we're definitely more years the yel only
has one year many years but the years
are disabled I don't know why we really
even have ears ears are very cheap yeah
you get great deals on years coming
digit key
Subash two eyes well survivor eyes two
eyes two eyes hey what did they want to
test something out covering the cabin
distracted it yeah that's right don't
cover the camera my friend said he
needed a he donates he stands a lot to
come by for research and development
yeah
hell yeah every Tesla seriously yeah we
take it we'll take your free Tesla what
is it
yeah which which doesn't top and don't
tell Tesla about this if you guys don't
under the out pearl Tesla doesn't like
us having our cars as the parties worked
pretty well well we forget the Tesla
maybe we can support so finally if
somebody donates us a Tesla yeah I would
be okay with that
good it's like the bounty program but
reverse yeah we'll meet you
I want a pencil they all let me by
guys this is the secret conversion of
all compiler that doesn't make mistakes
it doesn't
is this how good it is for everybody
it's pretty close to what everybody has
except they talk limit there
no I think this tonight whatever these
parameters are it's just we getting
better as we've been driving doing away
with the on this one is nobody yeah I
like this your cost okay it's higher
frequency and it more feels like yeah
like the car is doing something instead
of just meaninglessly wobbling me around
the lane yeah yeah we had a big we had a
big wobble fighting yeah after the last
few days we it's like it's not the wall
but that everybody was used to before
but still something was there
well yeah wasn't model counties do model
the old wobbles
doesn't know where it's going
that way that's not the monetary require
calibration actually no you know you
know where the head is you do some math
you figure out the orientation
[Music]
but yeah so what's gonna be enabled is
whether you enable driver monitoring or
not the net is still running and so you
will be able to get a summary of whether
you're paying attention regardless we
send back don't worry don't worry it's
not the front camera data it's literally
six numbers talks about the position of
your head how large your head is and
where your head is
maybe we'll post what Donna lady has a
largest head
[Music]
how do you do that scabies
how many mines have been mapped if I'm
getting partner
love me
and sighs leaderboard that sighs later
bud
big headaches
ya know see you like it when you're
comfortable like and actually that thing
does help look like I'm looking at the
iana that says I fear distracted
yes she's got I think
yeah disengagement
Wow I have to hold the wheel right today
we'll do it we'll know we didn't try to
exit but what's happening distracted
yeah we're you know sort of I was
looking here I guess I was distracted
yeah we'll wait longer till we get to
until they can't do read but then read
is fatal I mean that's what it's
supposed to be right like your head
means that you have to
okay doesn't drink the next day I guess
whatever engages slowly
like what great song
this Acura is running a coma pedal we're
running the couple guys the common pedal
is great it makes it a stop ago so guys
we don't get like dis engagements have
been reduced to like one or two per
track well he was stopping at any cable
right out
what type to cigars which I learned like
the driver my turn although the the
fading alertness a new mechanism or
introducing
it's just temporarily unavailable
because of what we write again oh yeah
yeah yeah they wanted you Justin
beeps in this car loud nice yes this is
the best car she's the best reserved for
the VP the CV kid not sure why then I
use it to be more like Betty trigger
yeah it's very we can also take anything
more for like a head down rather than a
head after especially because the press
is gonna be looking at that's a good
plant and headed down is what matters
more yeah no one uses a phone like this
don't have that info
if I tilt my head like this well I think
that maybe should be along I know I
tried to just teach you I shouldn't do
it because I usually got it at all yeah
that's actually shouldn't care about the
yeah pinko is pretty good ah yes what a
guy was saying that P Park is actually
good on current development parachute
yeah
or just chef replace release today guys
we want your applause
I went does two ever monitoring working
total darkness this is why iris love the
3-minute timer yeah yeah we need to up
the phone back beautiful three minutes
no more six guys and I got swelled with
the sex screening
alright Skokie's thank you for joining
us on this driver monitoring adventure
this is where we leave you pop double
use my phone it's angry I'm distracted
I'm distracted we'll leave with the
beeping no